DEIBIS JOEL AGUILA CALLE

Contact

Email:

deibisjoelac@gmail.com

Git:

@deibisjoelac

Linkedin:

@deibisjoelac

Languages

Spanish – English (basic)

Summary

Software Developer. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP OOP, JavaScript, CSS, VueJs, Angular, Ionic, Tailwind, MySQL, C# . Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- PHP
- Laravel
- Python
- Django
- Angular

- Innovative
- Service-focused
- JavaScript
- VueJs
- C#
- SQL
- Ionic Framework

Experience

Software developer - 06/2022- currently, **Medlink.la** , Perú Full Stack Web con Laravel, VueJs MySQL.

Software developer -12/2021- 05/2022, Galotech , Perú Full Stack Web with Laravel, VueJs MySQL, C# .NET

Software developer - 06/2021 to 11/2021, **Restaurant.pe** Perú Programmer Analyst.

Web Application Development Using Angular, Ionic, Tailwindcss, Rxjs, C#, wpf

Full Stack developer - 06/2019 to 05/2021, Sistemas SGE, Perú Programmer Analyst, Systems oriented to Desktop environments, Using C #, MySQL technologies.

Web Application Development Using Laravel, VueJs and MySQL technologies.

Full Stack developer - 01/2017 to actually, Freelance, Perú

Software developer - 08/2014 to 12/2014, KIPUSE, Perú

Administrative Assistant - 05/2010 to 04/2011, SUNAT, Perú

Education

Informatics Engineering- 2018 UNP, PE-PIURA System analyst- 2013 PE-PIURA

Certifications

Python Intermediate Course – Platzi.